<QuestionForm xmlns="http://mechanicalturk.amazonaws.com/AWSMechanicalTurkDataSchemas/2017-11-06/QuestionForm.xsd"  xmlns:xs="http://mechanicalturk.amazonaws.com/AWSMechanicalTurkDataSchemas/2006-07-14/FormattedContentXHTMLSubset.xsd">
  <Overview>
    <Title>
INSTRUCTIONS, INFORMATION SHEET AND REQUEST FOR INFORMED CONSENT
    </Title>
    <FormattedContent><![CDATA[
    <p><font size="5"><b>How (not) to name an object -- Instructions</b></font></p>

    <p>
        We asked various workers to <i style="color:#0020C2;">"please name the object in the bounding box"</i>, for a number of images.<br/>
        We need you to evaluate the names we got:
    </p>
    <ul>
        <li>Is each <b>name adequate?</b> (See definition of "adequate" below.)</li>
        <li>If not, <b>what's wrong?</b> Did they enter a word that doesn't apply to object they intended to name? Did they name an object that doesn't fit tightly in the bounding box? Did they misinterpret the picture? Something else?</li>
        <li>And <b>which object</b>, exactly, did the different workers intend to name?</li>
    </ul>

    <p>
        When judging if a name is "adequate", you <i>must</i> use the following definition:
        <br/><br/>
        <b>Definition:</b> A name is "adequate" if there is an object in the picture, <i>tightly</i> circumscribed by the red bounding box, that one could reasonably call by that name.
        <br/>
        Note: Sometimes parts of the object are not visible -- for instance parts which are behind some other object, or which fall outside the picture frame. Such invisible parts are allowed to be outside the bounding box.
        <br/><br/>
    </p>

    <p>
        In the task, you can hover your mouse buttons/icons for definitions, examples and clarification.
    </p>

    <p>
        This batch of HITs contains quality control items. <b>Submitting low-quality responses will lead to rejection of all your HITs in this batch.</b> We are reasonable humans though.
    </p>

    <br/><p><font size="5"><b>INFORMATION SHEET AND REQUEST FOR INFORMED CONSENT</b></font></p>
    ]]></FormattedContent>
<Text>
RESEARCH PROJECT: AMORE: A distributional MOdel of Reference to Entities (Universitat Pompeu Fabra – Barcelona – SPAIN).
PRINCIPAL INVESTIGATOR: Gemma Boleda.
FINANCED BY: European Research Council (European Union).
SURVEY CARRIED OUT WITH THE COLLABORATION OF: Amazon Mechanical Turk (AMT)

PART 1. INFORMATION SHEET

Purpose of the research
    • The research aims at creating a database of linguistic expressions which name objects in images, in order to come to a better understanding of how people use language, with the possible long term goal of improving human-computer communication. 

Procedure description
    • You will see images and various names that were gathered from workers in an earlier round, who were asked to name the object in the bounding box in the image. You have to indicate if any of these names are "inadequate" according to a given definition, if so, to indicate what's wrong about the name (multiple-choice), and finally to indicate which of the different names were intended to name the same object. The goal of the object name collection is to better understand how people use language; in particular, to understand the inventory of names humans posses for common objects. Please make sure that the object name does not contain obscene language. We reserve the right to block the participation in the project if you do not comply with this requirement; in this case, you will not be reimbursed.
    • You can work at your own pace. 
    • We did our best to ensure that the images will not contain any controversial material (in particular, we did our best to exclude any depiction of violent or sexually explicit scenes). However we assume no responsibility for the content of the images presented.

Privacy and data handling
    • Your AMT WorkerID, together with the ratings you produce during this experiment, will be available to the researchers of the AMORE project, who have committed to handling it in an anonymous and confidential manner. These data will be stored in UPF, Barcelona (Spain), and will be retained during the life of the project (up to 31 January 2022) and for five years afterwards for auditing purposes.  If you wish your data to be removed, such that they cannot be used for the project, please get in touch with Gemma Boleda (gemma.boleda@upf.edu), specifying your AMT WorkerID.
    • The data we collect, in an anonymized form, will be uploaded onto the UPF repository (https://repositori.upf.edu) and on the project’s web site (https://www.upf.edu/web/amore) webpage to be consulted and used in other projects by other researchers worldwide, and shared with collaborators.
    • Research results will be published in journal articles, conference presentations and via any other mode of scientific exchange and dissemination that will be seen as appropriate by the researchers, always protecting the participants' anonymity.
    • By accepting to participate in this survey you hereby grant UPF an irrevocable, perpetual, non-exclusive, transferable, fully paid, worldwide license (with the right to sublicense) to reproduce, distribute, publicly perform or display and transform your task results such that they can be used in this research project and they can be made available through the project’s webpage and the e-repository, such that they can be reused worldwide. 

Voluntary participation and freedom to withdraw from the research
    • Your choice to take part in the research is entirely voluntary. You are completely free to choose not to participate, or to withdraw from the study at any moment without any consequence.
    • This study was evaluated and approved by Parc de Salut MAR - Clinical Research Ethical Committee of UPF.

Potential risk and discomfort
    • If, at any time, you should become tired or feel other forms of discomfort, you can simply quit the survey. 

Benefits
    • For participating in this data collection experiment, you will receive a monetary compensation of 0.29$ per HIT. Furthermore, your participation will enable research on how we use language to talk about the world.

Potential reuse of the data
    • Only the task results, in an anonymized way, will be consulted and used in other projects by other researchers.

Questions? Write to us!
    • For any further doubt or clarification request, do not hesitate to ask! You can contact the principal investigator, Gemma Boleda, by sending an email to the address gemma.boleda@upf.edu.


PART 2. INFORMED CONSENT

    • I have read and understood the above information;
    • I have had the opportunity to have any questions about this study answered;
    • I understand and agree that my data (AMT WorkerID and task results) will be sent to and stored in UPF, Barcelona (Spain), and will be consulted by the researchers of this project;
    • I understand and agree that only the task results, in an anonymized form, will be shared with collaborators, uploaded onto the UPF repository (https://repositori.upf.edu) and on the project’s web site (https://www.upf.edu/web/amore) webpage to be consulted and used in other projects by other researchers worldwide;
    • I hereby grant UPF an irrevocable, perpetual, non-exclusive, transferable, fully paid, worldwide license (with the right to sublicense) to reproduce, distribute, publicly perform or display and transform my task results such that they can be used in this research project and they can be made available through the project’s webpage and the e-repository, such that they can be reused worldwide.
    • I confirm that I am over the age of 18. 
</Text>


  </Overview>
  <Question>
    <QuestionIdentifier>q1</QuestionIdentifier>
    <DisplayName>accept</DisplayName>
    <IsRequired>true</IsRequired>
    <QuestionContent>
     <Text>
    HAVING READ, UNDERSTOOD AND ACCEPTED ALL OF THE ABOVE, I DO  ACCEPT TO TAKE PART IN THE SURVEY.
    </Text>
    </QuestionContent>
      
<AnswerSpecification>
    <SelectionAnswer>
  <StyleSuggestion>radiobutton</StyleSuggestion>
  <Selections>
    <Selection>
      <SelectionIdentifier>C1</SelectionIdentifier>
      <Text>YES</Text>
    </Selection>
    <Selection>
      <SelectionIdentifier>C2</SelectionIdentifier>
      <Text>NO</Text>
    </Selection>
    </Selections>
    </SelectionAnswer>
    </AnswerSpecification>
  </Question>
</QuestionForm>
